twitiq.com 2010-05-22

# TwitIQ Smarter Twitter

Last revised December 28, 2009

TwitIQ Privacy Policy 

TwitIQ.com realizes that privacy is an important issue for our users. This document outlines the type of information that TwitIQ.com ("we," "us," "TwitIQ" or "TwitIQ.com") collects when our users use our services, and the steps that we take to safeguard your information. 

Information Collected by TwitIQ.com

TwitIQ.com collects various pieces of information on our servers in the United States when you use our services. Some of this information collection happens with your permission and some of it happens implicitly as you use our services. 

  * Your Twitter Username

To access TwitIQ.com, we redirect you to Twitter.com to authorize your username and password against Twitter's servers. Twitter then redirects you back to TwitIQ.com with a token containing your Twitter Username only. Your Twitter Password never passes through TwitIQ.com's servers. 

  * Your TwitIQ.com Session Cookie

You must enable cookies in your web browser to utilize all of the services on TwitIQ.com. When you login to TwitIQ.com, we store a cookie in your web browser that uniquely identifies you to the TwitIQ.com site. 

  * Your Interest Profiles

When you view and create Twitter content on TwitIQ.com, we will record keywords to build your interest profile. 

  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When you use our website, we record and maintain a log of requests sent by your browser to our web servers. This information includes information such as the URL that was used to view our website, your PC's Internet Protocol address, and the timestamp of the request. 

  * Twitter Web Service APIs

TwitIQ.com utilizes Twitter's web service APIs to authenticate, access, and update your Twitter activities on your behalf. Your Twitter activities conducted through Twitter's web service API's are governed by their individual privacy policy, not by TwitIQ.com's privacy policy. 

  * Google Search APIs

TwitIQ.com utilizes Google Search API's to provide web, news, and blog search services. Your Search activities conducted through Google Search service API's are governed by their individual privacy policy, not by TwitIQ.com's privacy policy. 

  * Third Party Advertisers

Advertisements of third-party advertisers may be displayed on TwitIQ.com. If you choose to click on an advertisement or link, TwitIQ.com may provide non-personally identifiable information to the advertiser and/or web publisher. Also, the advertiser or web publisher may use cookies or other technologies to collect information when you are visiting their web sites. The information advertisers or other third parties collect is governed by their individual privacy policies, not by TwitIQ.com's privacy policy. 

How we Store and Use your Information

  * Your Twitter Username

We collect your Twitter Username and associate it with your TwitIQ.com session so that we can identify your actions to invoke Twitter's API's. Your Twitter Password never passes through TwitIQ.com and is not stored on TwitIQ.com servers. 

  * Interest Profiles

Keywords related to your Twitter activity will become part of an internal interest profile that will be used to generate recommendations throughout the TwitIQ.com website. This profile may also be used to provide other personalized TwitIQ.com services. 

Keywords in your interest profile derived from activities that are displayed publicly in your Twitter updates may be displayed in your public profile. However, keywords derived from private Twitter activities will be kept private and never shared publicly on the TwitIQ.com website. 

  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information

TwitIQ.com may use non-personally identifiable information we collect to improve the quality of our services - for example, by diagnosing service or technology problems, by assessing and maintaining security, by increasing ad placements on web pages that are receiving more web traffic and presenting you with ads that we think you would be interested in seeing. We may also use the information to count and recognize returning users. This information will not be made available to third parties for promotional purposes. We will periodically delete this information to minimize the history of your actions on our website. 

TwitIQ.com may conduct research on the non-personally identifiable information collected to determine user demographics, interests, and behavior and may market the TwitIQ.com service by sharing non-personally identifiable information with potential advertisers or partners. If it does so, TwitIQ.com will share the non-personally identifiable information in such a way that users are not identified. For example, we may provide demographic or usage information to an advertiser so they may see how many registered users are from a specific geographic area or clicked on a certain ad in the previous month. TwitIQ.com also may provide your non-personally identifiable information to contractors so that they can perform services for us. 

  * Security

TwitIQ.com makes significant efforts to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the collected information. These measures may include the use of secure server technology. Be aware, however, that the Internet is not 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted over the Internet, and we accept no liability for any disclosure. 

  * Information Sharing with Third Parties

TwitIQ.com will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties. We may collect aggregate data on our user base, which may be shared with third parties. This information will only be disclosed in aggregate form and will not uniquely identify you to third parties. 

TwitIQ.com utilizes PayPal to process PayPal and credit card transactions. When processing PayPal transactions, we re-direct you to the PayPal service which collects and processes your PayPal authentication and credit card information. TwitIQ.com does not retain any PayPal user information or credit card information. Please see PayPal's privacy policy for more information on their privacy practices. 

  * Other Sharing of Information

TwitIQ.com may release information when necessary to comply with the law or a court order or an investigation. TwitIQ.com also may release information to law enforcement to protect its rights, property, or other interests, including those of its customers or users or to prevent illegal activities or violations of TwitIQ.com's Terms of Use. 

In the event that TwitIQ.com, in whole or in part, establishes a partnership with another company, or is acquired by or merged with another company, collected information may be transferred to the partner or the acquiring or merging company. 

  * Child Protection

TwitIQ.com does not offer services to, or target, persons under the age of 13. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we receive from people we believe to be children under 13 will be purged from our database. 

  * Links to Advertisers and Other Web Sites

TwitIQ.com may contain links to other web sites, including advertisers. In addition, user submissions may contain links to other web sites. TwitIQ.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web publishers, advertisers, or other web sites that may be linked to the TwitIQ.com site. 

Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy. Please check the effective date to determine if the privacy policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Whenever we make significant changes, we will post advance notices on our website before we actually make the changes. 

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at support@hanperson.com.
